bloggybootcamp.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy - The SITS Girls

Sway Group LLC (“Sway”) respects your privacy. This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) applies to the treatment of personally identifiable information submitted by, or otherwise obtained from, you in connection with the websites noted below (“Websites”), . The Websites are provided by Sway and may be provided by Sway on behalf of a Sway licensor or partner (“Services Partner”). By using or otherwise accessing the Websites, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with this Statement, please do not use our Websites. This policy applies to the following websites administered by Sway:

  * http://www.thesitsgirls.com/
  * http://www.bloggybootcamp.com/

**WHAT INFORMATION DOES SWAY COLLECT and How Is It Used?**  
The Websites collect the following types of information from our users.:

**Viewing the Site**  
We may receive and store certain types of usage-related information when you interact with the Websites, including but not limited to, your computer’s IP address and browser information. The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

The Websites use cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described below. No personally identifiable information is stored within these cookies. If you would like to opt-out of the use of cookies, review the settings on your browser.

**Advertisements**  
We use the Sway Ad Network to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Websites, which may use cookies. No personal information is shared with the Website’s ad providers.

**Audience Analytics**  
The Websites use Google Analytics to track statistics regarding our audience and Website traffic. No personally identifiable information is transferred from the Website to Google Analytics. [For more information on Google’s Analytics privacy policies, please visit this site](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). Additionally, the Websites use WSAnalaytics and SimpleReach Analytics to track statistics regarding our audience and Website traffic. No personally identifiable information is transferred from the Websites to these analytics services.

**Leaving Comments and Entering Sweepstakes**  
We may receive and store information that you voluntarily submit through the Websites for the purpose of leaving comments on blog posts or administering sweepstakes, contests or promotions. Examples of information collected for this purpose are your name, email address and website URL. This information is only captured when you voluntarily enter or opt-in and enter this information for collection.

**Newsletter Subscriptions**  
We may receive and store information that you voluntarily submit through the Websites for the purpose of subscribing to the Website to receive newsletters. We collect your name and email address, which is stored with our email service provider, [Mad Mimi](https://www.godaddy.com/Agreements/Privacy.aspx). This information is only captured when you voluntarily enter or opt-in and enter this information for collection.

**Submitting Content for Publication**  
We may receive and store information that you voluntarily submit through the Website for the purpose submitting a blog post for publication. This information is only captured when you voluntarily enter or opt-in and enter this information for collection. All submissions to the Websites are governed by our Terms of Use and [the specific terms for Submissions](https://swaygroup.submittable.com/submit/35833). Your personal information will be used to attribute the submission to you.

**Affiliate Marketing**  
From time to time, Sway engages in affiliate marketing programs. If you click on an affiliate link to make a purchase, Sway will receive a commission on that product. To track your purchases, a cookie is placed on your browser for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

Sway is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Websites will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

**Third Party Ads**  
From time to time, the Websites may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google or Facebook, in order to market the Websites. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Websites. At any time, you may opt out of Google Ads by modifying your Google Ad settings.

**Purchases**  
The Websites offer products for sale in an ecommerce environment. Personal information for payments are collected through Stripe and are subject to [their Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy/). Personal information regarding payments is not stored by Sway.

Some personal information, such as name and email address, are securely stored by Sway for purposes of order fulfillment and customer service.

**Event Tickets**  
From time to time, the Websites will offer tickets to events, which are available for purchase through Eventbrite. Personal information such as your name and email address, will be transferred to Sway for administering the event. Payment information is processed soley through Eventbrite and is not stored by Sway. This information is subject to [Eventbrite’s Privacy Policy](https://www.eventbrite.com/support/articles/en_US/Troubleshooting/eventbrite-privacy-policy?lg=en_US).

**HOW DOES SWAY USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?**  
Sway uses the information described in this Privacy Statement (i) internally, to analyze, develop and improve its products and services, (ii) to improve and support our marketing efforts, (iii) to display content based on your interests, (iv) to send you communications, (v) to respond to your questions and concerns, and (vi) as set forth below in the “Will Sway Share any of the Personal Information it Collects” section below.

**SERVICES PARTNER TREATMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.**  
Sway may provide personal information to an applicable Services Partner, as described above. The Services Partner’s use of your personal information is subject to the Services Partner’s separate privacy policy – and not this Privacy Statement. The applicable Privacy Statements have been linked above for your review.

**WILL SWAY SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?**  
Personal information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone (with the exception of sharing your information with an applicable Services Partner – see the “Services Partner Treatment” section above). We share your personal information only as described below.  
Services Partners: We will share your personal information with an applicable Services Partner (see the “Services Partner Treatment” section above).

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Sway’s agents do not have any right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of personal information for the above purposes.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Sway, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Sway goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Sway may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Protection of Sway and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Sway, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

**CHOICES FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
You can decline to submit personal information to the Websites at any time, in which case you may not be able to access the Websites. You may request deletion of your personal information by Sway by sending an email to swaylegal@swaygroupllc.com, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements.) When we delete the account information, it will be deleted from the active database but it may remain in our archives.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Sway features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**CONDITIONS OF USE**.  
If you decide to use or otherwise access the Websites, your use/access and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Illinois state law.

**THIRD PARTY SERVICES/WEBSITES.**  
The Websites may permit you to link to other services or websites. Such third party services/websites are not under Sway’s control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Sway of those other services/websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of such third party services/websites linked to the Websites are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Sway is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?**  
Sway allows you to access the information in your profiles, such as newsletter subscription or your profile for submitting content for publication, for the purpose of viewing, and in most situations, updating that information. This list may change in the event the services providers. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete and current, but we depend on you to update or correct your personal information whenever necessary.

**CAN CHILDREN USE THE SERVICES?**  
Our Websites are not intended for children under the age of 13. Sway does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13 and believes that children of any age should get their parents’ consent before giving out any personal information.

**SECURITY.**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We use commercially reasonable safeguards to protect your personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at swaylegal@swaygroupllc.com.

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Sway transfers personal information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Statement followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.**  
Sway may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Statement when he or she uses or otherwise accesses the Websites after such changes have been first posted.

**QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS.**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Websites, please send us a detailed message at swaylegal@swaygroupllc.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: May 2, 2016
